that uh last night talk help
you and uh I hope that tonight talk
help in your
life so last night we were talking about
um how to find a partner who can you can
trust
and we gave
example then when you first meet
somebody uh everything is very
beautiful and you think oh all the boy
which I met before was bad but this one
is this one is
good
and you feel big
hope the old ones uh they always have
some
problem but this one is
different this one I can
trust he loves me as much as I love
him
and he will be good to
me and the boy also think the same thing
about the
girl they are thinking oh before I met a
nice girl but each one has a little bit
of
problem but now this new one is 100%
good and you feel very
happy uh for about 6
months uh then uh one day uh we gave
example you call they call you from the
workplace and they say uh I'm sorry I
can't come for dinner I
will uh because I
am working
late then they
hesitate then uh you can feel the
hesitation people can
feel uh in our uh where we are staying
we are staying
at there's a small there
cat and uh they they took the cat from
the street he was
sick so Street cat is very smart
cat if they want food or anything they
have to have to be very smart to find it
no one's going to give them
food
so they become a good judge of
people this person will be nice to
me this person will kick
me uh so our cat in life CER is a street
C we came from
America with our many suitcases
usually C doesn't like new person with
suitcase they don't
like make lot of
no most c will run
away but Light Center C is a
street he's looking this ging my
looks
good he will give me some
food so he didn't
move C understands uh people's nature
without
talking and we all have this
ability in English I don't know in
Chinese but in English you say I can
smell
what
so husband call
me tonight I
am working
late the wife is like Street
Camp they can hear something there
something uh not 100%
true maybe he's going to have drink with
his friend
or then Begins the first small crap in
relationship uh First St
then usually
get and then maybe don't trust the
person then you start to doubt
everything they say I'm going to the
movie with my
friend then you start to
worry maybe they not telling truth
you then the C starts to get bigger and
bigger then you start to have bad
feeling about your husband or your wife
you start to have bad feel
about part is
there when you look at them you are
eating dinner when you look at
them before you feel Big
Love now you look at
them you you like
Street not sure what feel feel something
bad about
this so this is the same as
ASP you have to understand
ASP if I teach you about
ASP then you will understand your
husband okay
so what is this thing this is a
uh I think I don't know
someone I didn't
try but uh you say this is a headache
medicine what is the meaning of
medicine why why will I eat this
what will you
say
yeah if I don't have headache I don't
want to e
this today someone C for me
pineapple
C if I uh want to
eat if I want want to
eat I will eat pineapple cake I
like I don't have to eat
this this only for one
reason when I
have then I should be with
me why don't I eat a
stone
when I
have
why
headache stone is not
medicine the meaning of
medicine is it will help the
head it will work from the
heaven so on the
television you can see many
advertisement new Extra Strength
ex
new this one is better than the other
one
if you take this one your headache go
away in one
hour they say one very bad
thing they said this one really
works what does really
mean why do they say really
work cuz the other one doesn't work
does the other one
work all
work yeah sometimes work sometimes
work okay so sometimes work sometimes
doesn't
work so we came to Taiwan on AA
Airlines and
uh before that we went to
VI uh we went to Canada to take the
airplane then
uh we start to get on the
airplane
and they said no no cannot
go we said what's wrong he said
volcano in
Iceland and you cannot
fly said we wait few
hours four days we are waiting for few
hours they say okay okay come come we
have to f
we go to the
airplane they said no no you s few
hours four
days in the
airport then on the fourth
day they
said uh okay we are
going this is first airplane to
Europe everybody get onpl
then we asked the
St is it safe to
fly she said we think
so there uh we got in the
airplane but they didn't take
off then one uh guy came they open the
airplane underneath
they are taking out all the
bags it means we wait one hour
in then we said what's going
on they said four people decide not to
get on the
airplane we have to take off
their for
security
why did the four people didn't get on
the
airplane because St said I think
so then they think I think so it's
not maybe fly maybe fall
down so when you are getting on the
airplane
air the St say to
you usually the plane is flying very
good
sometimes then you won't get on
Earth
say
sometimes sometimes
doesn't if it doesn't fix
heav is it
medicine you have to say
no looks like
medicine they put in the
medicine also here say
medicine
but on the day that you eat and it
doesn't
work on that
day it's not
medicine and this is not
medicine and this word medicine is wrong
okay on the day which this doesn't
work is the medicine
here you have to say
no at that time it looks like
medine it's in
medicine world is
medicine
but
really it's not
medicine why why am I saying
this because I said your husband is the
same as
the you have to
remember we are sitting at the dinner
table you are looking at your
husband this husband call
yesterday he said I
am working
late and you are looking at the
husband like a street
C then you see husband maybe he
not
uh then you have to check page
two in uh the first thing it
says you are at dinner
table you are looking at
your you are thinking
maybe I'm not sure he is telling
me that husband that you are looking
at he's not
husband
okay
same thing he
is there is no
husband you to say
no why looks
like he
not husband is the
same the husband who is not telling you
the truth is not there
top of this
page someone is not
there who is not
there your husband is not
there you are looking at
somebody last night he called
you I am working
that
person not
there
why what
itan
is is
husband what's it
mean next
one
when you look at your
husband he is not being
honest you think he's coming this
way he is
not you don't take I am making
him you don't think I am making
my husband come home from
work he comes in the
door you
think he came in the
door in the word also he said he came in
the
door everybody believes that word he
came in
dark it's
wrong this says
medicine also
wrong this is not
Medicine husband did not come in
the you made
H you brought
that he's coming from your mind
husband who is not telling you the truth
is not coming from
husband the husband who is not telling
the truth coming from
you
why
next next
page number
one uh you are sitting in a
home husband is late
forward husband call
you I'm
work
then you you hear like
uh he is talking some problem in his
feel some
problem then uh later you find out he's
not telling the
trth your friend say oh I saw your
husband last night he was at the water
then you think then you feel
s you say why why are you doing
that why why he say that thing to
me what
happened then you have to
understand it's not coming from you
it's coming from
me this is bad
news how how is coming from
me
before number
one someone trust
you someone believes in you
someone has hope about
you and then you broke the
TR you lie to
them for
example there is one person at your
work you don't like them so
much little bit
stupid she said to you she she said
let's go to
then you say
tomorrow 1:00 I
promise we will go to lunch
together actually don't like
that but you say okay tomorrow we will
go to
1:00 tomorrow she comes new new
outfit she did good make
she's very excited to
go you don't feel like
going so you say uh I'm sorry boss gave
me extra job today I'm sorry I can't
go you told a small lie
you broke
trust to break the
lunch and to break the
marriage different
thing lunch is a
small lunch is 1
hour
marriage is a big
thing marriage is 30 years 40 years 50
years when you break a
lunch you put a SE
in it's like put the seed in the
car
I I am very happy now I'm started a
garden in my
house I'm planting
roses you buy the r from the
store it's about this this
big
just there's no
flower there's
no when they gave to me I said no no you
made a mistake I want
roast no no this is
a said
no
no he said no you don't
understand you put
water
FTI
done it will
grow it will grow B of three
me and it will make many many
roses so the the seed is very
small I planted in
February I came to taian in
December
I went back I pled
my it's a little
stick when I come to the airport uh four
or five years
ago in the morning I bring my back to
the
taxi I look at my
RO
first
I this is very good
Lu and all the leaves are big now it's
about
this so the the seed is
small it stays in the
ground I don't know what they do in
the I can't see what
they but it's
amazing something happening
inside in 3 four months it's
big the seed in the mind is the
same you tell a small you break small
trust about
l
this is only one hour breaking
TR after one
month I don't know what it's doing in
there I don't know I don't
understand it's like
rose I don't know how the flowers stay
inside I don't
understand
but something is happening
inside you broke 1 hour lunch
trust it could SE in the
M after one
month SE
open
you get phone
call tonight I
am
working this is the
C you you broke
trust
small it stay inside the
M it gets bigger and bigger
then you get very bad
very this is not one our trust
broken this is many days of
trust so now I ask you a
question when you look at the husband in
the dinner table
you are looking at the husband who
called you last
night is he out
there the husband that you see out there
the husband who came in the
door he does not
exist is the meaning this is a
meaning is it
ask
it sometimes it work
why does it have uh something
inside that fix the
heav most people they will say yes yes
inside look here it says active
ingredient there's some ingredient
inside
of course uh medicine has something
inside there's something
inside it helps
you that's why we don't eat a
stone medicine is not the same as a
stone stone doesn't have active
ingredient this has active
ingredient if I eat
aone doesn't take away
heav if I eat
the does it take away
heav
sometimes sometimes
I I will tell you something very
important you have to
understand if you understand this your
whole life will be
successful anything you want in your
life you can
get you can get
money I did I did
it you can get Young
I also
do accept
here
uh and you can you can have good
part but you have to understand one
thing inside
the medicine there's nothing no AC
nothing
if you help the other
person today my friend they said I have
headache they want to take a
medicine they want to take a
massage I want to tell them no no you
have to eat chocolate chip cookie
that's medicine
for
uh I want to help
you I try to help I didn't do very good
job okay I I I know what to
tell I didn't do good
job but if I good
job put
in they have
headache I try to help
them he put a seat in
my then I
get I'm going to take
this will it work or not
why not because there is a chemical in
it's not because of
that you know
that because sometimes work sometimes
not
work the power of the medicine is not
inside
the the active Med of the medicine is
coming from
me if I help that person today I didn't
help okay I didn't do good job I'm sorry
but if I help
him it could SE in my
life I I have
H sometimes I get
H
then I I have to
I
me take like
this if you help the other person
before it puts this power into the
medicine if you didn't help the person
the medicine is
not why am I talking
about we are talking about your
husband who put the LIE into the
husband's
mouth who who put the I am working
tonight it's not it's not in his
mouth it is not coming from
him you
put if he
Li
you put
there if he tells the
truth you put
there now I have very important question
for
you you are putting the LIE into your
husband you are also putting the truth
into your
husband
which one do you
want do you want husband who
life or do you want husband who
tell which which one do you
want everybody wants the
truth husband also wants the wife to
tell the truth
so you have to put the truth
into how do you put uh Power into
Min help the other
person who has
headache don't be
like
didn't help the person
today later he's going to take many as
they won't do
anything
really but now we have an important
question how to put truth into the
husand how to put truth into the
life
they don't have a
power you can talk to them for many many
this you have to tell me the
truth never lie to
me you don't call me from work and say I
am
working I know you went to the bar my
friend told
me
is this a good way to put the truth into
your
husband
no
why it doesn't
work no it's worse than
that sometimes work sometimes doesn't
work you get into the
airplane Maybe it will
fly maybe it will fall
down you fight with your
husband you have to tell me the
truth maybe it will
work maybe it
won't this is wrong method bad
method we want the correct
method how to put the truth into the
husband's
love
keep it
in for whole
life I'm going to show you one
way let's do a little
meditation
uh sit up
straight shoulder should be shoulders
should be equal not like
this head should be nice
straight some
meditate
please
relax some people meditate like
this not
relax
so is
okay like
this back
is hand hand you can do left
hand and then
right but if you feel more comfortable
you can like
this see what you like
work if you feel
hot uh this is I think
easier if you feel
cold this is
better you have
Choice okay now we will medicate So
Close Your
Eyes watch your
PR we will take 10 breath
just watch your
breath
to
for
e
now we will
start please keep your eyes
closed this meditation is to put the
truth in your husband's body
or it could be your
wife could be your
sister could be a
friend could be father or
mother could be your
or you choose no
choose one person that you want them to
be truth to you they tell truth to
you you choose one person
another
step there eight
steps number one
step please think about one good thing
about
that
what is the best thing about
that think about it
now
step number two
a in your mind give them some gift
beautiful gift
something which they
enjoy
e
number
three think about any mistake that you
made with before you made some
mistake
tell them I'm sorry I made this mistake
and I'm
sorry for
example Michael can say today I'm sorry
I didn't take good
of down down
pon
step number
four think of about a person you know
who tells the truth most
and in your
mind thank god oh you are such a good
person you always tell the
truth I want my husband to
be think about you know who
all
e
number wish
what this person does to know good or
bad everything they do to you should be
like a
teacher
should
e
step number
six ask this
person
h the
dance
most
important
you think in your mind if you are you
think maybe
my if you are
CHR so think maybe my husband maybe
his maybe
he's
e
that's when you think about your husband
or your wife and you think
maybe when you do all these seven seven
St
now take
that give it to you another
one somebody you know is
having
I will give you
my
something give
to help the other person who is having
trouble
they
e
open
your uh I will give you two ideas about
this
med uh this meditation you can find page
four and page
five
I want you to look at page
number uh second
thing uh how to see other person is
with you need to practice
I give you a good
example
uh I want long time ago I want to start
my own Diamond
business then I don't know anything
about
that I thought I will go to work in the
store for a few
years
they will teach me about The
Bible and I can start my
own so I went to the first
store I said can you give me a
job they said uh do you have experience
in
business I said I don't
he said do you have salesman
experience I said no
I actually I'm but I cannot tell
them then they said is your family your
father your
grandfather
I said no
nobody they kick me
out this happened 30
times 30 I went to 30 stores they pick
me
up the last one
very almost K
me to treat then I found
uh the new man
started and he gave me
job that came this $250
million now sometimes I
thinking those 30 guy who KCK me
up they must be
Buddha I'm so happy you kick me
out if you didn't kick me out I will be
in a small store I will be working for
my whole life with one
two
they keep me
out in my company uh on a good day we do
300,000 diams in one day
wow we have a t many
tables and the diamond is like this p
it's a lot of
fun you can hold the
DI then I think about the 30 guys who
hurt me before kick me
out you are real thank you thank
you so when someone give you
trouble you have to think maybe they are
good maybe they can see
future they are pushing Michael you go
out from the small store you are in one
year you will find a big
business
maybe the people who give you trouble
are are they pushing you to good
place maybe your husband is teaching
something maybe is going to help
you so during this step number
this is most
important I think maybe maybe this
person
is if you think like
that it puts a new SE in
your after
that they will become person with truth
in their
mind
don't get angry of them oh I am working
late don't get
angry it puts
bad don't get
upset in your heart you say maybe maybe
something good is
coming
maybe they
are there's very famous
story uh I was with my friend she is
here tonight her name is
Jame uh we went to uh American Embassy
two days
ago do you
know you get Mo
L American he called
Starbucks so we went together to
American we got
coffee and she brought her
friend he's very very very
good
and we spent several hours very
fun uh talking about one beautiful Tower
in
China and the architecture of this
Tower uh in 1981 I think the tower fell
out it's very
old underneath they found found a finger
from
budha it's a very under
the then I was thinking about a story I
heard a
story one woman in
tiet she's very
old and this happened several hundred
years
AG
and her son said I'm going to
India I want to see the holy
place where the Buddha was teaching
before she doesn't like to see the boy
go long trip
dangerous but she said okay you can go
but one take don't
forget you bring me back
something I want little piece of
Buddha's body something something to
something you for
me I
allow so he went to
India it took 6
months he had a really good
time then he came back
to he came back to his
town he start to walk to his mother's
house oh
no I forgot the piece of
Buddha he saw a dead dog kind
then
he he pull out the
tooth then he put in very nice
CL and he brought home to
mother look I found from P
from mother said thank
you she put the tooth on the office
every day she get
medications
mother actually
this but
mother maybe husband is a creep creepy
guy bad
guy
maybe husband is not good at
all maybe just stupid
guy but if if you
believe if you think maybe he's trying
to help
me maybe he's pushing me to the 30,
300,000 he's pushing
me
if you
believe if you think maybe he's
Buddha if you do this eight steps of
meditation he will
change he will tell
truth because he's coming from
you
okay now you can have
refresh I I also broke my
trust to
you I said first thing today we will do
questions I
forgot so uh when you have
refreshment
you can write down some
questions uh can be English can be
Chinese
okay uh then you can give
to can you stay okay she will stay
here and then I will answer the question
after the break
okay and then if you want to sign a book
or you want a picture or you want to
tell me anything you can come
okay I think I promise J to
me so please turn the light on so people
can
see have a nice
ref
oh
okay so uh question is uh I have
business and I have uh many people
working with me in the
business but I have uh some trouble to
open my heart to
them uh do not feel like
family
so how to open my heart for
them I suggest uh you this page
number
seven uh these are seven
steps you can try the seven
steps I will do uh
quickly uh we did four steps
yesterday no we did yeah we did four
three uh now we will finish all I'll do
all with
you this also help with your husband to
tell
truth it also help if you want to open
your
heart step number
one this is not the only life which you
have lived
in
why I come from
America I grew up in a Christian
country
you they don't talk about uh I have life
before or I have life after they don't
talk about
that so in our country uh no one believe
they have life
before No One Believes you have life
there but I heard
something when you look at the sky in in
the
night where I
live uh there is no
City I live on the
mountain it's very
dark you can see thousands and thousands
of
stars if you use the
telescope I heard in one
inch
there are 100 million
stars 100 million stars in one
AG if you have good
CC so I think in those place should be
other world more more people should be
somewhere I think
so uh we didn't meet them
yeah but there are so
many should be at least one or two other
places in tiet there was a
fog he lives in the
well he's the king of the
we he is this
big he's the king father of the whole
world then
one day a crow came to the
well and the Frog said I am a
king all this water I
King CR said you are king of this
water I am King of the big
water CR said I want to show you
something he pick up the f then he
fly he took the Frog to the
ocean he put the Frog on the side of the
ocean frog look at the
ocean and they say in B they say his
brain
explode he thought the well was a whole
world we think oh T is big F
uh this planet is very big
place there are million million like
that there are people like us many many
many
world people say I only live One
Life Time time has no
beginning time has no end
you have been here million million
times you will be here again million
million
times this life is
nothing in the million times
before you met we met together
new I know your
faith in my heart I feel I know you from
before
I met each of you million million
times sometimes I am
teacher sometimes you are
teacher sometimes I am sitting
there sometimes you are sitting
here we did millions of
times and each one of you has been my
mother not one
time not times million
times you I came from your
body million
times I drank from your milk his milk
also
million million
times so I should take care of
you you
me you gave me life Millions
times I should thank you I should take
care of you and you should take care of
me
also uh so this is very famous this
seven uh if you want to open your
heart answer for this
question you think about the
Stars you think about the
ocean I hope your brain doesn't
explode but we have been here many many
million
times the people in your company was
your
mother this will open your
heart so think about
it uh if you think more and
more it will open
I heard this teaching in India in
myama he gave this teaching to
me I was uh
22 I left uh from the mountain he taught
me on the mountain
I went to the Indian
town to get some
food small place in the
mountain first guy I saw was very
dirty very
old very
sick then I saw
him then I remember
this and I thought oh he is my mother
also he also was my
mother then my heart
open then I one day I C for him
something
F uh I took to his very poor
house I gave him
food and he told me you
stay and then uh he start to teach me
to everything he taugh me
were that's why I am
here that's why I can't get
here he taught me how to
talk so if you meet
anybody you think oh this person was my
mother maybe it's something big will
happen your heart will
open
question
the question is I'm married I'm doing
spiritual training and my my wife is as
well and her train the practice with
traditional religion and now I met
someone that I feel connect spiritually
connected for those of us who have
children and it's hard to make a
decision in this
still uh I have this question many
times uh about uh four weeks
ago my good
friend uh she came to me
uh she is my friend her husband is my
friend and uh she told me I have
question for
you uh you know I like my
husband he's a good
husband but uh I have another friend I
met he teach me some uh spiritual
thing and I feel very strong
connection and I want to stay with
him I don't want to stay I love my
husband he's good
man but then this other person I feel
such good
connection so I'm thinking to leave my
husband what do you
think I have a policy my my mother gave
me policy he taught me
policy we don't make decision for other
people I don't say you should leave your
husband or you shouldn't leave your
husband there was one student my Lama
had one
student you know his name was Michael
Wick he always come to ask my m a
question
I have a chance to buy new
apartment but I also like my old
apartment but the new one is a good
comp but the old one is very
comfortable you can talk like this for
half
hour then my Lama gave
answer you decide
so I think it's a good
policy I didn't tell her you should
leave your husband or you shouldn't
leave your I didn't
say I just said one
thing I told her I'm not going to make
decision for
you and I'm not going to say this is
good or this is
bad but I can tell you one
thing what you do to other person will
come back to you
say what you decide to do to other
person then the new person is going to
do it to you I can
guarantee and I said do go
think and she called me after one
minute I
just you see because if you hurt your
husband to go to a new
person 100% guarantee new person will
hurt
you new person is
fun new person is
interesting but it won't
work what you do to other person will
come back
you so when you have to make decision
use use
this you have
responsibility you have to be a good
person you made promise to one
person if you keep that
promise
maybe maybe chance will come with other
person you
see
it's
interesting if you keep your
promise what you want will
come if you break your
PR to get
something you will lose
it if you keep your
PR what you want will come to
you this is uh
nature this is
La uh
keep your
promise don't give promise
easily after you get promise keep your
promise if you keep your promise what
you want will
come because you kept your
PR if you break your promise to get
something you will lose that
you have
a I mean
can give me one
temporary okay I think
that uh you I say in English and then
Jessica say Chinese how
my dad has a drinking
problem he got
drunk he lost
control he hit
mom I can't
forget this
picture I was very
scared he is nice to his
grandchildren but I don't know how to
forgive him
and I don't like to be alone with
him my uh father also have drinking
problem uh I saw this many
times so I
understand
I have many uh Christian
friend and uh in the
Bible
uh the people ask Jesus
question I like his
answer it's a good
answer I'm a
Buddhist but I like like to read his
answerers very
good somebody has said to
him if someone hit you on the
faith what should you
do he said you like to hit me here
also it's a very
difficult then they said if someone uh
steals your uh
sweater uh
take your
sweater you have to ask them
question would you like my
also this is very
difficult then one more
question if someone hurt
me should I forgive
them he said
yes then the question asked how many
times
seven
times said No 7 *
7 490 times I
counted
why uh they are coming from you they
coming to
that uh when you see a person get drunk
that
when you see them hurt your
mother that is a mirror that is a
mirror you are seeing
yourself deep deep deep
down you have some
anger you have
some
violence everything you see is a
mirror if you meet a good
person this is coming from
you if you meet a bad
you if you meet a person who cannot stop
drinking it's because you are doing a
small thing which you cannot
stop I know what for me it
is I cannot stop to eat
chocolate if I see chocolate I have to
eat I go to today to someone's
house we are talking about my
charity they have chocolate in the
room I'm talking to them
but difficult to talk to
them because I'm I'm always looking at
the
chocol I have a chocolate
addiction uh it's a small
thing to break the lunch date with your
friend for 1 hour is a
small the rose uh seed is a small thing
everything gets
bigger what you
do you will see in in the
world and it will be
bigger your father's drinking may be
coming from your chocolate problem
really your father's drinking
problem may be coming from your chol
what should you
do what should you do to stop the
father's
thinking stop the
Chate stop what you
do
sming don't break the lunch
date don't lie about lunch
day husband will begin to tell the
truth what is your
addiction stop
it Father's dreaming will
St but
but it takes
time seed has to
grow your father is hurting your
mother you have
responsibility you have to also you have
to stop
it you can't you can't allow people to
hurt other
people you you can't say oh I I'm
waiting until 6 months my seed has to
grow
mother I'm
sorry I I don't cannot help you for six
months my SE has to
grow you also can do
that at at now before the SE
grow you have
responsibility you have to try to stop
it you have to say
something you have to try to uh protect
the
mother this is your
responsibility will it
work will it
work will you be able to protect
her sometimes
yes sometimes
not the seed always
works after 6 months
always
work what you trying
now maybe
work maybe it might work but you have to
try you have to say
something you have to protect your
mother don't be surprised if it doesn't
work but
try at the same
time CL a new seat stop the
chocolate stop hurting people small
small hurt
stop 100%
Works in six
months but now you have to
try you have to try to protect your
mother if it's very bad you have to
please okay or talk to the uncle or
something
protect uh maybe one more okay okay
uh how do we burn out The Bad
Seed it's a very very good question
we have two
jobs we have to make new good
seeds and we have to destroy the old Bad
Seeds
uh let's say uh you want a husband to
tell the
truth
then uh mainly you have to tell the
truth so about small
things uh your husband is telling you I
have
to work
late then not telling you 100%
truth how to change that
you have to tell the truth
yourself you don't tell big lies now I
understand many people told me I I I
don't
lie I tell the
truth my husband tell big
lies I never tell
you that's like saying the tree is very
big but I don't understand the seed is
very
small of course the seed is smaller than
the tree
always so you have to be
careful uh don't tell the small
lie uh if you want the big line to
stop you have to stop the small
L someone say uh thank you for making
soup for
me uh but taste a little bit
burn then you want to
lie you want to say uh oh I think my
sister here she cooked a little bit too
long
actually sister wasn't there
today you burn the
soup you don't want to tell the
Pres to lie about burning the soup is
not a big
lie to lie about your marriage is a big
Li to lie about the soup is a small Li
but if you are very
careful oh I will not likee even about
the soup I will not
lie you start to
lie uh I didn't bring the soup my
sister
you in we have University in
it's a free
University no charge it takes 14 years
to
finish uh this year we will graduate
first
graduation 130 uh
students uh they finished 14 years this
is first uh
graduation in
June then they have a lot of experience
they heard this thing many
times and I very
happy when we have
conversation we are eating together
everybody is
talking like
this who burn the
soup everyone is stopping
with
it becomes very strange
conversation the line wants to lie all
the
time they always they are very
careful they start to say he's a
stupid she
is then it's very beautiful to
me many have
sentences because they are watching the
small
things when the small life start they
they are cutting their own
mouth to control this
one it's harder to control the big
truck he's very
tricky but if you learn to
control then the the old seed will
die oh my husband is telling me
something
notest it's coming from
me I have to stop the old
SE how to stop the old
se you stop
li small Li about the
soup it will kill the old
seed what you don't okay this is my last
thing
okay my last
advice then we are coming back in
December
okay we can talk some
more uh because we like the pineapple
cake
uh better than chocolate I
think maybe New
Addiction uh I give you one last thing
okay what you don't
like from other
people you stop doing
yourself be